Painterly Pack Customized Pack
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
by rhodox
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
Unless noted otherwise, all graphics in this pack were edited and created by me. A few textures were generously provided by various individuals and are included in the pack with permission. These individuals are credited under their individual contributions on the web site (www.painterlypack.net). The default paintings are NES sprites, and so belong to whoever made those games, I suppose.  

This is a Customized Loadout file, and as such, has only the options selected by the user that created it installed. If you would like to access or experiment with the other alternate options available, or the original loadout, then you will either have to download the standard pack, which contains all the options, or create a new customized loadout with the new options.

This pack may be used freely in whole or in part by any owner of Minecraft, and combined with other texture packs, so long as credit is given and no profit or donations are solicited through that person's use of my textures and skins. You don't have to credit me if you use it with your youtube videos or promoting your server or things of that nature, but it's appreciated if you do.

The pack is given away freely, however, donations for the time invested and ongoing development and testing of The Painterly Pack are extremely appreciated. The Donate link can be found on at painterlypack.net, and if you got it from anywhere else, it's not the official source and probably out of date.

Finally, of course, a thank you to Notch for creating such a terribly addictive, endlessly entertaining game!




Directions:
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
1. Using the built-in utility in the Minecraft game itself, open the minecraft texture folder, and place the Painterly Pack zip into that folder from wherever you've stored it.
2. Select the Painterly Pack from the list of texture packs.
3. Enjoy!