the Cel-Pak: TRON Grid
version 1.2

by thetonestarr


Now Minecraft Beta 1.3 compatible!

Latest update includes numerous bugfixes, customized Beta 1.2 and 1.3 graphics, and a variety of minor touchups. 

Unless noted otherwise, all graphics in this pack were edited and created by me. Pieces of a few graphics have been derived from Painterly and Ptolatar's Texture Pack. Thank you each for creating your wonderful texture packs. Painterly can be downloaded from PainterlyPack.net. Ptolatar's Texture Pack is available at MinecraftWB.com.


Finally, thank you to Notch for creating this fantastic game!



Directions:
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
1. Using the built-in utility in the Minecraft game itself, open the minecraft texture folder, and place the Painterly Pack zip into that folder from wherever you've stored it.
2. Select the Painterly Pack from the list of texture packs.
3. Enjoy!